# .RWD

#### ROWENA DINATA

# **ABOUT ME**

My name is Rowena Dinata I was born 1987, I am a graphic designer based in Jakarta, Indonesia. I have seven years of experience related to graphic and web design. I eagerly still learn more to update my soft skill and I am looking for a chance to achieve it.

# CONTACT

Mobile:

+628973451928

Whatsapp:

+628983216261

Website:

http://rowenadinata.github.io

Email:

rowenadinataagmail.com

### SKILLS

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR	••••
ADOBE PHOTOSHOP	••••
HTML & CSS	••••
JAVASCRIPT	••••
OFFICE	••••
DRAWING SKILLS	••••

# **EXPERIENCES**

**UI DESIGNER** 

**ALTASTRATUS - TANGERANG** 

2013 - 2016 Altastratus is a startup company based in USA & Indonesia. Founded by 4 people who are enthusi-

Indonesia. Founded by 4 people who are enthusiastic about IT and automotive. My role is to create the design for printing and digital things and do the basic HTML and CSS for the

website.

MARCOM EXECUTIVE

PT. ERES REVCO - JAKARTA

2012 - 2013

PT. Eres Revco is a cosmetic brand company that owns the Revlon and Ultima II brands in Indonesia. My role is to do all marketing collateral such as flyers, print ads, and other things

related to promotions.

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER** 

PT. CAHAYA PERDANA PLASTIK - JAKARTA

2011 - 2012

PT. Cahaya Perdana Plastik is one of the market-leading companies for plastic homeware in Indonesia. My role is to do all the design things for promotion and for product printing

collaterals.

JR. GRAPHIC DESIGNER

DESIGNCUB3 - JAKARTA

2009-2011

Designcub3 is a creative design company that does all the creative things from printing to digital and social media promotion. I started as an apprentice and continued as a junior graphic designer after graduation.

# **EDUCATION**

UNIV. TARUMANAGARA

**BACHELOR OF ART** 

2005 - 2010

I majoring in communication visual design and most of the curriculum is the theory and basics for graphic design with a little bit of esthetic theory, art history, and management.

# SHORT COURSES

DICODING.COM

BASIC WEB PROGRAMMING

2022

FRONT-END WEB FOR BEGINNER

BASIC JAVASCRIPT